Is the man who did this
still in the building?
He ran off.
I don't know who else is in here.
- Hey. what do we do?
- You know him?
We bring him in at least once a month
for prostitution or possession.
Calls himself Rabbit.
Two options. I arrest you or you come in
right now and cooperate fully.
How long you been clean?
Four months.
You do it on your own?
Look. he cares.
My sister was taken.
I only got six years with her.
but I knew her.
They believe her disappearance
is linked to sex trafficking.
There are pictures. sightings.
Was there a sighting in Chicago?
Yeah. that's why I came here.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[PHONE BUZZING]
- Voight.
- Hey. Hank.
How's it going?
Can't complain.
You got something good for me?
No. no case for you. I just...
something else
I wanted to ask you about.
You got a new partner?
No. why?
Got an intelligence officer
I don't know using your name.
sniffing around vice. looking for
any new working girls that
match a certain description.
What description is that?
30s. dark hair. Spanish speaker.
Iranian descent.
might not identify that way.
- This officer go by Imani?
- Uh-huh.
Look. she hasn't given us a case number.
but she's asked for about
30 open case files.
Is she being a problem?
She's being real persistent.
won't give me an RD.
Is this an off book thing?
I can't have these cases out there.
It's just a cold case
she's working herself.
She won't be a problem.
OK. just wanted to check.
I'd never heard of her before.
And like I said. she's real persistent.
Hank?
Yeah.
All good. I hear you.
Hey. let me know if you
catch something for me.
OK. I will.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Get in the truck! Drive!
Hey. police! Chicago Police.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
Go. go. go!
Stop!
Police. stop!
5021. Damen and 13th.
on-view burglary in progress.
Hey. no. stop!
I got one down. I need an ambo.
Offender fleeing in a blue F-150.
Partial plate. Boy 2 3 David.
westbound on 13th.
I need some cars.
- Hey.
- [WEAK WHEEZING]
I got you.
Hey. it's OK.
I'm here to help you.
You're gonna be all right.
[CRIES]
I know. I saw.
It's OK. You're gonna be all right.
It's OK.
[POP MUSIC]
♪ You and I. you and I ♪
♪ We just can't get enough ♪
♪ Ooh. ooh. ooh. ooh. ooh. ooh ♪
♪ Ooh. ooh. ooh. ooh ♪
♪ We just ♪
Hey! Yo!
What the hell happened?
Did they take my ATM?
5021. cancel that ambo.
- Are you police?
- I need a mobile crime lab.
Hey. are you police?
Where the hell are those cars?
Did they take my ATM?
I put a tracker in that thing.
Copy. 5021. crime lab en route.
Additional units two minutes out.
[SIREN WAILING]
Beat 913 is on scene.
But I want you to take over
as soon as you get there.
Am I looping in Burglary/Homicide?
Yeah. for priors. but we're taking this.
And get me that woman's particulars.
She is just walking across the street.
She's got kids.
Anyway. I'm going to make
the notification myself.
Copy you.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[LOUD POP]
[SCREAMS]
Chicago PD!
[GROANING]
Police!
[GROANS]
Hey!
Chicago PD! Let me see your hands.
Is anybody else here?
- Hands now. now.
- I don't think I can.
I think I lost my hand.
I can't... oh. God...
Answer me.
Voight?
Rabbit?
No. no. no. no. no.
you got to be kidding me.
No. oh. man. what... ah. ah. oh God.
[GROANING]
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
- Move.
- What are you doing here. man?
- OK. I can't lose my arm.
- Rabbit. answer the question.
I can't be one of those dudes
with too few limbs.
Who are you working with?
OK. I am not going to be sweet about it?
I'm going to have
a whole bad attitude. OK?
Hey. No one goes in or out.
I don't want any heat on that place.
- My officers are on the way.
- Wait. what?
- Keep walking.
- No. no. no. you got it wrong.
OK. look. I didn't break nothing...
- Sir. we can take him from you.
- He's fine.
He just blew up his hand. Let's go.
What? I just told you.
I didn't rip that ATM.
So you don't gotta go in there
and do the whole...
Don't gotta what? Do my job?
Come on. let's go.
Rabbit. you're bleeding
all over the lawn.
- Let's go.
- [GROANS]
OK. all right.
OK. OK. OK. wait. no.
you're coming with?
Wait. no. he doesn't need to come with.
I'm fine.
For goodness sake.
I'm not an idiot.
I knew my place was ripe.
Look at the glass.
it's right up on the street.
And I do good business.
I get a lot of cash.
You say you put a tracker inside it?
That's right. [CHUCKLES]
They weren't going to get on top of me.
not after I heard about the other three.
One was right down the block. you know?
So I knew not to mess around.
- Uh. um...
- I got a good tracker.
I got my cameras.
Right. the names of
the three establishments?
There's Bucky's.
that's right over there.
one block over.
It made no sense.
They ain't got cash like I got.
They do a couple of hundred a night.
- Yeah. and...
- And the owner. he's...
- he's not well.
- Mm.
And the other two?
There's Tarmack's and Briarwood.
that new spot. you know.
the one with the four-tops
out front trying to look fancy.
Again. no one's going to have
cash at a place like that.
Imani.
- Oh. wh...
- Excuse me for a moment.
Wha...
Monologue for every answer.
Burglary/Homicide
confirmed four similar hits.
same MO. same stats.
They're sending over footage.
All right. well. that matches
with Longwind over there.
- He said there's three he knows about.
- Good.
Hey. who has ears in?
Hey. I'm here with Kim.
Ah. hell! What the hell are you doing?
- I need you to stay still.
- You get that bar footage yet?
- That hurts.
- Yeah.
There's cameras inside
and outside the bar.
Was it... was it any good?
- Oh. God. Oh. God.
- [INDISTINCT SPEECH]
What? I can't hear you.
- Rabbit. stop!
- Oh. I'm sorry.
- Am I bothering you?
- Say it again.
Oh. God.
It shows two men. masks and gloves.
- They broke in first.
- OK. OK. OK. all right. just...
Was one about maybe 5'10". about 180?
OK. well. I'm 6-foot. you dick.
- 170 lean.
- No. Neither matches those specs.
I already told you
I didn't jack nothing.
OK. I am a cracker.
That's what they call it. OK?
I just crack the things open.
That's all I do.
Voight. you get that?
Girl. you're not done yet? OK...
- Yes. I got it.
- Do it a little nicer.
Just a little softer. please.
OK. just... OK. yeah. yeah. yeah.
OK. oh. my God. what is it?
Oh. Jesus. I need to keep my arm.
[SIREN BLARES]
Oh. God. Oh. my God.
- Come on. Rabbit.
- What do we got?
Who dropped the ATM off at your place?
You gotta save my arm.
Burns to the dorsal and ulnar.
Started IV fluids.
gave morphine for pain.
No. no. they barely
gave me anything. doctor.
- He's an addict.
- I am a sober addict.
Oh. it was a sober choice to
strap firecrackers to an ATM?
Can we turn it down?
Oh. hey. look. look. look.
I need you to save my hand.
- 'cause I'm an artist.
- Rabbit.
I'm going to take good care of you.
I draw. So I just... I need...
OK. OK. where's your phone?
Where's your phone?
What? I don't have a phone.
- Come on.
- Get off of me.
- Just tell me.
- Voight. Voight.
Enough. enough.
This is where you leave. OK?
He's my patient now. We'll call you.
- Just leave.
- He's a flight risk.
I want him cuffed to that bed.
Doc. can get him out of here?
- Oh. God.
- On my count.
One. two. three.
OK. OK. OK.
- Hey.
We got anything yet?
Voight's already radioed twice.
- He's on one.
- Nothing clean yet.
Blood's still being tested.
but I'm sure it's Rabbit's.
Who is this guy?
Ha. he's a CI of Voight's.
Caught him in
a narcotics case last year.
- He just keeps popping up.
- Mm.
House is leased to him.
Landlord says he lives alone.
Hmm. real genius.
Any witnesses see this thing get dumped?
No. it was still early on.
so he must have used the alley.
Might get lucky on footage. though.
He have company last night?
I don't know.
Voight wants us to clear out
after we search the place.
put TACT on in case these
guys come back for their cash.
Yeah. copy that.
- Notification?
- [GRUNTS]
All right. tell me we have something.
Footage from Burglary/Homicide
all matches to a T. It's our guys.
It's their fifth hit in eight weeks.
Any other bodies?
No. but only because they got lucky.
There was never anyone else out.
So no witnesses either.
But MOs all match.
First. they break
into the establishment.
chain up the ATM.
rip it out by brute force.
It's the concrete screws.
They know they don't have time
to get them out. so ram raid.
All the ATMs stolen were private.
What about the truck?
Past three came back hot.
So did this one.
stolen out of Hegewisch.
No footage of the theft.
Owner confirmed it was there last night.
And then it's gone.
We're still digging into this Rabbit.
I'm running his known associates.
but he doesn't have
a phone registered to him.
And no financials to speak of.
You know. Rabbit's pretty skint.
He's got no bank account.
His social media is all art photos.
Well. he knows these men somehow.
and there's gonna be evidence of it.
I mean. he can't keep his mouth
shut to save his life.
- [PHONE BUZZES]
- He'll have talked to somebody.
Rabbit?
This is real nice.
Thank you so much.
One useless hand isn't good enough?
- You want to be cute?
- Oh. yeah.
'cause apparently
you're my fairy godmother.
- Oh. my God.
- Popping up unannounced.
trotting me off to hospitals.
Oh. yeah. we are real cute. honey.
Who's robbing the ATMs?
Oh. so you believe
that I didn't do it now?
Who is robbing them?
Do you know that you made
them give me a tox screen?
Wanted to see if I was
a lying about using?
Who's robbing them?
Bro. what do you think we have here?
Nothing.
The men you're working with.
they killed a woman.
plowed her down with a truck.
didn't even slow.
Didn't try to avoid her.
And they could have.
[GRIM MUSIC]
OK. You know I wasn't there.
- To the law. you were.
- To the law?
Yes.
You know how this works.
You are gonna help me.
You are gonna be my partner.
whether you want to or not.
You don't have a choice.
♪ ♪
It was like mincemeat.
you know Hamburger Helper?
- Mm.
- It was just like that.
All right. deals arranged.
You are officially
a cooperating informant again.
Oh. great. congrats to me.
All right. so who are
the two masked men?
Well. I only knew one of them.
And like I said.
I only ever cracked the things.
Well. get to the name.
Deon Rollston. Dude's a dick.
But he's a pretty good rip-man. so...
And you don't know the name
of the other one?
No. Like I said. OK. I crack the ATMs.
and I'm a pretty good cracker.
which is why they hooked me in.
Yeah. pretty good.
Yeah.
Yeah. no. that's sweet.
Seems like you two have
the same sense of humor.
I'm so glad he found
another one of himself...
Have you ever seen the second rip-man?
- No.
- How is that possible?
'Cause they aren't idiots.
OK. they drop off the ATM
right after they jack them...
[GASPS] ...with their masks still on.
Who do you hand the money to?
Deon. he's the one who gives me a cut.
You never heard a name. a detail?
No. it's like a one-minute transaction.
OK. they ram the thing in my back door.
then run the hell out.
All right. well. do you have any texts?
Whoa. you didn't just
hear my joke there?
Oh. jeez.
Rabbit. do you have any texts.
calls. recording. anything?
No. I don't record
my criminal liaisons...
Well. then you're working him.
What? No. no. no...
- You heard me.
- I-I just gave you his name.
- So now you go pick him up.
- I can't.
- You're an unreliable CI.
- Oh. I am reliable as hell.
Who is giving third party
information on a case
he is working off.
We need real evidence. Rabbit.
You're working him.
- Yeah. I've heard that before.
- Mm.
[HUMMING MELODY]
How long you known this guy?
Not long.
Well. he seems to know you.
He's real comfortable around you.
Hmm.
Hasn't struck me that many people are.
What is he doing?
Don't know.
Well. it shouldn't be taking so long.
He's got the cash. What is he doing?
If you want me to go check. I can...
[HUMMING MELODY]
- [DOOR OPENS]
- Oh. man.
[HUMMING MELODY]
All right. Rabbit's got the cash.
We're a go.
Come on.
Oh. he's always late.
Hey. yo!
[SIGHS] This guy.
They're making contact now.
We got clear eyes.
- 'Sup man?
- Copy you.
- What's up?
- [LAUGHS]
- Wrong hand. man.
- Oh. you fool.
You blew yourself up. didn't you?
I told you to use a damn crowbar.
OK. well. explosives are faster.
Yeah. and they blow you to bits. fun.
- Yeah.
- [LAUGHS]
Come on. I want a shot first.
What. bro? Come on.
Hey. come on. little stumpy.
[LAUGHS]
- Come on. bruh.
- Come on!
Oh. God.
When I tell you to do something. do it.
- Where are we going. bro?
- Don't worry about it.
- Come on. man.
- It's a surprise.
We weren't planning on going mobile.
He needs to take ownership of the cash.
Hold it tight. Follow. We'll take lead.
Copy you.
[ENGINE RUMBLES]
Good morning and welcome in.
Let us know if you need anything.
Hey.
You want something?
My treat.
Little stumpy must be hurting you.
- [LAUGHS]
- Man. no. prick.
Come on. let me just give you
this back so I can go.
Why you in such a rush?
You got some big plans
I should know about?
You know. uh...
Bruiser texted me.
Bruiser. that's got to be
our second rip-man.
He said he wants out.
Weird. huh?
You know. I [...] he wants to make...
[AUDIO CUTTING. INDISCERNIBLE DIALOGUE]
- ...talking about...
- Oh. you know
[AUDIO CUTTING. INDISCERNIBLE DIALOGUE]
Hey. are you losing audio?
[AUDIO GARBLING]
Um. it's jumping.
[NO AUDIO]
No. wait. audio's out.
- We got nothing.
- What's going on?
I don't know. Signal's fine.
Boss. you want us to move in?
[TENSE MUSIC]
Go in and ghost.
- Imani's got it.
- [SIGHS] OK.
♪ ♪
Hey. good morning. Welcome in.
Let us know if you need
help finding anything.
Will do.
That would be idiotic.
now. wouldn't it be?
Hey. look. I get it. OK?
All right. I get it. I understand.
[CRASH]
- Oh. oh. my God.
- Hey. what's happening?
Oh. my gosh.
Is he OK?
[STAMMERING] Oh. I don't...
What?
I-I don't know what's wrong with him.
He. uh...
he said he wasn't feeling good.
JoJo. call 911.
No. no. no. no. no. no. no. no. no.
Uh. I think he's just... he just sick.
Um. there's a lot of blood in there.
I'm just gonna go
get something for the...
I don't think you should move.
Stay still.
Can you hear me?
No. you shouldn't move.
It's just ringing.
♪ ♪
- Yo.
- What the hell are you doing?
- I don't know.
Hey. man. what's your friend's name?
Uh. name's... Charlie.
Yo. what are you looking for?
I'm looking for a key
to the scissor gate.
He's casing the ATM.
OK. this is the diversion.
He's insane. I told you.
Hey. man. what you doing back there?
Find it. Hurry up. Hurry up.
Um. I just. uh...
♪ ♪
What are you...
I was getting something
to stop the bleeding.
Did 911 answer yet?
- Where's his friend?
- He's. um. getting him water.
I can help him. I got him.
I got it. I got it. yeah. yeah.
Hey. man.
- Oh. my goodness.
- [GROANS]
Come on.
Let me see the COH.
OK. Jesus. here.
And what is this thing.
you didn't hear what he said?
Well. it wasn't working.
so that's why I went inside.
- Tell us what he said to you.
- A lot. OK?
He... he said a lot.
He said. um. well.
since Bruiser was out. I was in.
That was the whole thing with the key.
He needs the key for the scissor gate
so he can rip the ATM.
Bro. I didn't just
lose my mind in there.
Rabbit. what happened to your wire?
I don't know. Isn't that your thing?
OK. just tell us what else he said.
Look. Deon wants me to
rip the ATM with him tonight.
I'm supposed to meet him at 1:00 a.m.
I'm also supposed to wash the cash
from the last one. but... [SCOFFS]
Smartening up.
So who's Bruiser?
No idea. It's the first time
I ever heard the name.
You sure you never
heard that name before?
What did I just say?
No. never.
OK. well. let's go.
Don't we have a bad guy
to catch or something?
Standing there looking at me
like I'll tell you what I know already.
He's on ice.
He's requesting gyros.
You got nothing at all on the COH?
No. it dies 20 minutes in.
Kim's still sitting on Deon.
but without the COH. we got nothing.
We could still arrest him.
Press him. leverage best we can.
But the ASA might not be convinced.
Or we get an active furtherance.
All right. we got anything
on this Bruiser yet?
Alias brought up nothing so far.
I'm still running all of
Deon's mudds and tolls.
all of his associates.
OK.
We don't have a choice.
Woman died. I want it ironclad.
We'll let him move tonight.
Set Rabbit up.
We'll catch Deon in the act.
[KNOCKS]
What's up?
I checked the COH.
There's nothing wrong with it.
I think Rabbit might
have messed with it.
OK.
Why?
I don't know.
He was inside his house way longer
than he needed to be. We both saw that.
My guess is. he knows who Bruiser is.
and he's trying to work you.
So why the secrecy?
He's a CI.
If he's working me. he goes to prison.
Right.
[SIGHS]
It seems like you like him.
like you care about...
You don't need to protect me. yeah.
OK.
Should I go press him?
I will.
I'll take care of it.
Hey.
Got a fresh COH
and pen cam inside there.
Embedded this time.
OK? And what?
Like. show up and what?
Rip the ATM. That's your mask.
OK. well. that ain't really
what you want me to do. right?
Like rip it how much?
Like. what percentage
of ripping is allowed?
Just rip it.
It's better you don't know
when we're moving.
We'll arrest you both
and keep you covered.
I hate this. This is ugly.
Dang.
Rabbit. are you really still sober?
Your conversation skills
have not improved.
OK. there are things called sequiturs...
Are you?
Yes.
I already told you that.
You... you took my tox.
Who helped you?
What?
Last time I saw you.
you said you didn't do it alone.
So who helped you?
Yeah. well. lots of people. man. lots.
Rabbit.
There's nothing you want to tell me?
What is that supposed to mean. man?
Like what?
Are you going senile already? [CHUCKLES]
I mean. what am I supposed to tell you?
Look. I got nothing.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
OK. let's go.
He should be here by now.
Yeah. this guy's not keeping a clock.
TACT's still sitting on Deon's house.
No movement yet.
[RABBIT HUMMING MELODY]
[TENSE MUSIC]
Whoa. what's this?
Run these plates.
Still no movement on Deon?
No. but he could have slipped TACT.
All right. the truck's
registered to a guy in Oak Park.
It's got to be hot.
I'm sorry. baby. I know you
told me not to come. I just...
- I didn't...
- Go.
- What?
- Right now.
The police are here.
Get back in the truck and go.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Go. go.
Stay on the truck.
Everyone stay on the truck.
Damn it!
Imani!
♪ ♪
[HORN HONKING]
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[CRASHING]
Rabbit! Hey! Stop.
No. no. no. no. no.
you don't understand.
You're not understanding. Please!
Stop resisting.
♪ ♪
5021. Rabbit's in custody.
Adam. Kim. where are you?
Right behind you. Sarge.
♪ ♪
[CAR HONKS]
[HONKING]
I lost eyes.
He just took a turn.
He's heading West on Fremont.
Cut him off.
Copy you.
We're running parallel.
headed down 18th.
I'm moving on 20th.
I'm clear right.
♪ ♪
We're clear right.
Damn it.
Racine's clear. We don't have eyes.
♪ ♪
All right. Kim. Adam. call it in.
Get a BOLO out. Set a perimeter.
Copy you.
Gotta understand.
I swear. I was confused.
I just...
I wasn't expecting that man to be there.
- Just...
- He called you "baby."
Well. no. I... well. I can explain that.
I can explain all of it.
We heard him wrong?
No. I didn't say that. but I...
[ENGINE REVS]
My radio not working?
I was already in pursuit.
He ripped off the COH.
- He ripped off...
- I put another tracker on him.
- We wouldn't have lost him.
- Wait. wait. you did what?
You got an opinion on that?
I... [STAMMERS]
What is Bruiser's real name?
And if you lie to me...
- Come on.
- I swear to God.
What is Bruiser's real name?
Bryant.
Bryant what?
Bryant...
Bryant Evans.
How's he hooked with Deon?
He's his second cousin.
Look at me.
Get him in my car.
- You get in there with him.
- What... what...
- You don't understand.
- Loop in Torres.
Run Bryant. Run all his last knowns.
You have a warrant on standby.
I want to be able to move on this guy.
- [GRUNTS]
- Yeah.
- You gotta understand.
- No.
We are done with that.
- All right. give me your hands.
- All right.
Tell me.
who is Bruiser to you?
I told you. he is Deon's family.
OK. Deon forces Bruiser into this stuff.
You know?
But Bruiser. he's loyal.
so he feels like he owes Deon
'cause he helped raise him.
That is not what I asked you.
What is he to you?
Your partner? Your boyfriend? What?
He's all of that.
You tipped him off
when you're at your house.
when you're getting the cash?
Yes.
Does he live there with you?
Nah. nah. he just crashes there a lot.
Where does he live?
Where would he go right now?
Well. he crashes at. you know.
friends and family spots.
- you know.
- Oh. my God.
OK. he'd go to Deon's.
but please. Voight. please.
You asked me who got me sober. right?
Bruiser did.
You know. we keep each other straight.
Do you get that?
Like. you know. we got each other.
Look. please. he is not a bad man.
He drove over a woman.
OK. then he was scared and terrified.
Look. Deon. see. that's the parasite.
But. Bruiser. he's good.
I only started cracking those ATMs
to get Bruiser out of this.
Voight. I will give you
anything that you need.
I swear.
But you got to give him a deal.
You did it for me.
so please do the same...
or. you know. he can take mine.
Why would I do that for you?
Why?
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Because I know you're not unfeeling.
You ain't that person you pretend to be.
that... that... that... that ain't you.
I seen you.
We saw a guy die together.
And you got to understand.
having somebody
that makes you better. you know?
I know you do.
♪ ♪
Please.
OK.
- You have got...
- Look.
I will do anything.
anything.
We're going to Deon's right now.
Put this on.
Listen to me.
You're going to do exactly what I say.
OK.
♪ ♪
I promise.
You got away.
- I am so sorry.
- Are you OK?
Yeah. yeah. yeah. I'm OK.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
- What did you tell Deon?
- Nothing.
Baby. I didn't tell him anything.
But what happened? What happened to you?
They tracked me down after my hand.
I didn't know what to say.
Look. I knew that Deon
was going to give you up. OK?
They knew about him.
but they didn't know about you.
I just thought that I-I could play it.
It's OK.
But we got to find a way
to get out of this.
OK. then we will.
No. today. right now.
No. we've got to figure this out.
Rabbit thinks he's getting him a deal.
Mm-hmm.
I know you can work him.
Oh. good.
Because I don't need protecting.
Especially not when I give you an order.
I was already in pursuit.
You're not convincing me
you don't care about him.
Look. we're going to
go in there with Deon.
I'm gonna give him this cash.
You and I. we're out. OK?
We're getting the hell
out of this goddamn town.
Yeah. OK.
You think that's gonna work?
So what are you doing with Vice?
What?
With Vice.
Sergeant Wilcox called me.
said you were being persistent.
Wouldn't give an RD number.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
I...
Why are you asking me this now?
Why not? I mean. you need protecting?
No. I don't.
Yeah. that's what I told him.
I get it. Stay out of your business.
There you are.
I knew you'd come.
Been waiting for you to show.
Gun.
What the hell are you doing. bro?
- Yeah.
Don't play. Don't do that.
Why you call it off. Rabbit?
That's not what I told you.
Shut up. Bruiser.
Why'd you call it off last night?
And no. don't you say
another word. Bruiser.
Don't you dare.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Answer me. Rabbit.
♪ ♪
- You don't have an answer?
- Why are you testing me?
You blow yourself up.
Your little boy toy here
suddenly wants out.
And then you two don't even do
the job that I give you.
What do you think that adds up to?
You're trying to screw me.
No. I'm not.
OK. I saw you jack that ATM.
And I saw on the news
that you got somebody killed.
I don't want Bruiser
anywhere near you...
No. no. that's not it.
You're either screwing me. or he is.
No. d-don't... don't pull that out here.
- Back off! Hey!
- Rabbit! Rabbit!
[GUNSHOT]
[GRUNTING]
- Stop moving.
- I said get off of me.
Rabbit. what's happening?
What's happening?
- Rabbit. what's happening?
- Hey. hey. hey. it's OK.
Stop. stop fighting him. OK?
- He's gonna give you a deal. OK?
- Rabbit. you're good.
- Drop the gun.
- Just stop.
Rabbit. you're good. drop the gun.
Voight. you're hurting him. man.
- Just put him in cuffs.
- Hey. drop the gun.
- Voight. stop cuffing him!
- Hey.
- Drop it.
- It's fine.
- He's OK. It's fine.
Come on. man. you don't have to do that.
Just don't want him hurting himself.
Put the gun down. It's OK. Rabbit.
Now hand me the gun. Come on.
Put the gun down. Give it to me.
- Give me the gun.
- Rabbit?
Put the gun down.
Put it down. Come on. Rabbit.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
- Drop it.
- No.
- What did you do?
- Drop it.
Put it down. No.
- You... you lied to me?
- Put it down.
You said that... that
he could get my deal.
Rabbit. put the gun down.
No.
You're... you... you lied to me.
Rabbit.
You're not gonna shoot me. You're not.
We're gonna work this out.
Put the gun down. Rabbit. come on.
You lied. You lied to me.
Rabbit. a woman died.
It's not that easy.
But we will work it out.
Put the gun down.
- No. no.
- Rabbit. just calm down.
- Just calm down.
- You lied.
- Take it easy.
- You lied!
Rabbit. no!
[GRUNTING]
No. you lied to me.
You lied. Bruiser. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
You lied to me. You're a goddamn liar.
You looked me in my face.
and you used me.
You used me.
Oh. you're worse than trash.
You're an abomination.
- You're less than nothing!
- Hey. come on.
You're worse than nothing!
That's enough.
I will never forgive him.
Bruiser. I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry! [SOBBING]
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Hey.
Rabbit's been transferred.
I spoke to ASA... agreed.
kept the majority of his deal.
He won't be in there long.
Same can't be said for Bruiser and Deon.
but they lawyered up.
OK. OK.
Hey.
Since when are you drinking at work?
Since always.
- Nightcap.
- Mm.
That's pretty sad.
- Mm. what is that. scotch?
- Mm-hmm.
You got. like. a beer in there?
Shall we cheers?
No.
Thank you for booking him.
You'd have been fine. He's just a CI.
Who the hell cares. right?
Mm.
Did you have a lead?
[TENSE MUSIC]
Vice.
why you came to Chicago.
You have a lead on your sister?
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
"Lead" might be generous.
Hmm.
A man contacted the tip line.
Marine.
Said he didn't want to go on record
'cause he didn't want
his name tarnished.
He's a coward. really.
But...
he said he met Shari in Chicago.
Said...
She was working a corner and...
Told him when she was drunk
after a paid night. that...
she thought her name was Shari.
But that she didn't remember...
♪ ♪
Where she came from
or who she really was.
S-she matched the description.
And he was convinced. so...
Hmm.
Yeah. I know it's not a lot.
but I'm digging anyway.
♪ ♪
You want my help?
[WOLF HOWLS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm